it's a vibrational resonance
that is a particular frequency that i
recognize as not my own or at least a
much bigger part of me
and i sort of liken it to the idea of
two tuning forks
when you start one vibrating if they're
keyed to each other then the other one
starts vibrating in harmony and as soon
as they start matching frequency and
vibrating together that's kind of what
it's like
so the channeling class as i understood
it
ultimately was training you to shift
your brainwave frequency to a point
where you go into a state called gamma
which is about 40 to 45 or 40 to 100
cycles per second but i i stay in the
range of about 40 to 45 when i'm
channeling and then bashar makes an
adjustment in his brainwave frequency
and somewhere in the middle we lock
and as we vibrate together what you get
is a translation of his thoughts
into the language that i'm programmed
with so the idea of channeling
is not possession or anything like that
it is a synchronization of frequencies
that allow you to have the same thoughts
at the same time as whoever you are
vibrating on the same wavelength with
first and foremost you are always
manifesting something if you were not
you wouldn't have an experiential
physical reality correct correct
so the idea is you do not have to learn
how to manifest this is automatic
it's bashar's perspective that
if we understand the nature of reality
the nature of existence
we'll understand our nature better our
relationship to existence
why we're here why we experience reality
the way we do he is letting us know
that there is a way to take all of the
different things that people have been
talking about on earth for thousands of
years that might be considered
philosophies
or more recently new age concepts
and no pun intended bring them down to
earth
in the sense that
we are often left
with new age concepts that sound
wonderful
but what do they mean
what you are simply learning is how to
manifest more consciously to be more
aware of how you manifest so that you
can manifest what you prefer instead of
manifesting your unconscious beliefs
for example one of the concepts you hear
constantly in you know new age thought
or whatever you want to call it
is follow your bliss act on your passion
live your dreams
now that is a wonderful sentiment and
and it sounds great
but
where's the practical side of
understanding that concept how do you do
that how do you go about really living
your bliss and knowing that you'll be
okay knowing you'll be supported he
takes that concept follow your passion
and he starts breaking it down well what
is that what is that state of being what
is that feeling
you can think about things all day long
you can talk about them all day long but
if you not willing to actually act on
something that is supposed to be
representative of who you are what your
truth really is who the person is that
you truly were created to be
if you don't act on that you're not
speaking the language of physical
reality
you